[Music]
they say there's a time to learn things
well we say the time is ripe when you
decide it is
having invested in icic a Prudential
Freedom sip for 12 years Mr goal got the
freedom to sponsor grandson's Cricket
coaching
they say age makes you dependent we say
it makes you Mr and Mrs Dependable Mrs
Gomez slogged her life out but never
missed her monthly investment in icic
Prudential Freedom sip in the last 15
years now she invests her time and
monetary freedom in a passion for
photography
[Music]
we say life is for making moments count
life is for enjoying your freedom
how does it work
the Investments can be asked per your
convenience for example invest rupees 10
000 every month for eight years on
completion you start getting 10 000
rupees every month
invest rupees 10 000 every month for 10
years on completion you start getting 15
000 rupees every month
foreign
[Music]
Freedom sib you have the freedom to
choose your Investments your tenure life
you seek for yourself and your near and
dear ones
mutual fund Investments are subject to
Market risks read all scheme related
documents carefully